cucas.edu.cn 2019-10-10

# CUCAS Privacy Policy | Best Agent for Study in China | Study in China | CUCAS in China | Study in China | CUCAS

## Introduction

The security of our users' personally identifiable information is a high priority for CUCAS. This Privacy Policy applies to personally identifiable information collected by Beijing CUCAS Co., Ltd on its Web site at www.cucas.edu.cn.  We also act as an outsourced service provider for colleges, universities, nonprofits, and other organizations (referred to in this policy as our "clients"). When our clients collect information about you through the use of our facilities, their privacy policies and practices govern their use and disclosure of that information.

Personally identifiable information, which we call "personal information" in this policy, is information that directly identifies or is directly associated with an identifiable person. Some examples of personal information include a user's name, address, email address, citizenship, date and place of birth, and parents' names and addresses. Personal information does not include aggregate information or de- identified information. "Aggregate information" is information about the use of our Web sites, such as information collected about site users, or a category of services or users, from which any personal information has been removed. An example of aggregate information would be de-identified data indicating that forty-seven percent of the site's registered users have identified themselves as male.

## Overview

**Collection.** We collect personal information on our Web sites, such as when you register for and participate in our online application. We also collect personal information for our clients in the course of providing Web-based and email transaction processing services to them. We obtain this information via email and in "forms" that we host for our clients.

**Use.** When we collect personal information for a client, we provide it to that client. The client's privacy policies and practices, and not this policy, govern the client's use of that personal information. When we collect personal information on our Web sites, we use the information to complete the transactions requested by you, to administer, improve, and develop our sites and services, and for the other purposes described in this policy.

**Disclosure.** We do not rent or sell your personal information to third parties. We provide personal information that we collect for a client to that client. We do not disclose your personal information to third parties other than for the limited purposes described in this policy.

The remainder of this Statement gives more detailed information about our collection, use and disclosure of personal information, in addition to the measures we take to protect personal information while in our control.

### Personal Information That We Collect

We collect personal information from you when you voluntarily provide such information by registering for a CUCAS account. We require you to register for an account in order to fill out an application or other form we host for a client.

When you create a CUCAS account, we ask you to create a username and password and to provide your first name, last name, and email address. When you submit an application, or otherwise use our facilities to perform an action that requires the payment of a fee to the client (e.g., to pay admission application fees), we collect your electronic payment information.

We also automatically collect some information when you use our sites, such as your IP address (a unique number assigned to a specific computer on the Internet) and standard information included with every communication sent on the Internet. This information allows us to determine your browser version and type, operating system, browser language, Internet service provider, and which pages you view on our Web sites. All of this information may be aggregated and used for various purposes. It is not, however, used to identify you personally.

An application or other form is "in process" from the time you start it until the time you complete it. While it is in process, you may access the form and modify the information you have entered into it by following the instructions on the application or other form. Once you submit a form, you will not be able to access or modify the information submitted on that form through CUCAS.

### Use of Personal Information

We use the information you give us to provide the benefit, assistance or service you are requesting or would like to obtain. We may transfer aggregate or group data about our users for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage or other characteristics of our users as a group without disclosing personally identifiable information. By submitting your information to us and using our Website, you agree to allow us to transfer such aggregate data to third parties.

### Disclosure of Personal Information

We may disclose some or all of the information we collect, as described above, with affiliated companies and with third parties (i.e. nonaffiliated companies) as permitted by law. For example, we may disclose some or all of the information we collect with the following types of affiliated companies and third parties:

    * Companies with whom we conduct joint marketing campaigns;  
    * Companies that provide products and/or services, such as companies engaged in banking, credit cards, consumer finance, consumer computer products, travel, insurance, as well as other direct marketers and retailers;  
    * Companies that perform services on our behalf; and ther third parties as required by law, such as in response to a subpoena.

By providing us with your personal information, you are giving us your express consent to our disclosure of your personal information but only for the purposes described in this policy.

## Third Party Privacy Practices

While we strongly support the protection of privacy on the Internet, we do not have control over, and cannot be responsible for, the actions of our clients or other third parties. When we collect personal information in the course of acting as a service provider to our clients, the privacy policies and practices of the client whose form you have submitted will govern how that client treats your personal information. Our clients typically provide privacy statements at their sites describing how they treat personal information. We encourage you to review each such third party's privacy statement, if any, and to otherwise understand its privacy practices, before providing personal information directly to it or in our forms on which it is named. Additionally, you may be able to access non-CUCAS sites from our Web sites (for example, by clicking on an advertisement). When you leave our Web sites, the policies described in this Statement, along with all other CUCAS policies, no longer govern.

## Children Under 13

Our sites and the forms accessible using our technology are not intended to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old, you should not create an account with us, otherwise provide personal information to us through our sites or other services, or create any applications or other forms through our services.

## Cookies

We may use cookies to identify users and to customize their experiences. Our cookies contain no personal information about you. We use cookies to prevent you from having to repeatedly enter your login information, to save college and scholarship searches temporarily, to administer our Web sites and help us understand how visitors use them, and to improve our Web sites and related products and services.

We may use third parties, including network advertisers and other third party ad servers, to deliver ads to you. These third party ad servers may use cookies, Web beacons, or other technology to collect information about your visits to our Web sites and may use that information to present advertisements that may be of interest to you (including while you are no longer on our Web sites).

You may refuse to accept cookies by following the procedures specific to your Web browser. If you do so, your browser may react strangely and you may not be able to complete, save, or submit a form or use some services on our Web sites.

## Security

We use reasonable security measures in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, or alteration of personal information under our control. When you submit an application or other form through our sites, provide electronic payment information that we request, or log in to your CUCAS account, we use encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol, to protect such information while in transit. We provide any electronic payment information you provide to us on our sites or in our forms to our payment processor, and use SSL to protect it while in transit. We do not store it after it is transmitted to the payment processor.

Despite these measures, we cannot guarantee protection of all information against interception, misappropriation, misuse, or alteration, or promise that your information will not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others. We have no control over the security of Web pages we do not serve, for example our clients' sites or other sites you might visit.

## Correct/Update

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you can correct, update, or delete the information you have provided to us by: (1) logging in to your account, (2) modifying any of the fields, as desired. You also may contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below to correct, update, or delete your information.

## Unsubscribe

To stop receiving newsletters from us, please [Unsubscribe Instantly](https://letter.cucas.cn/nUnsubscribe.php).

## Changes in Privacy Policy

We will modify this Statement if our privacy practices materially change in the future. We will notify you of any such modification only by posting the modified Privacy Statement on our sites and indicating at the top of the Statement the date it was last updated. We encourage you to review the Statement each time you visit one of our sites, to see if this Statement has been updated since your last visit to make sure you understand how personal information you provide to us will be used.

## Contacting the Website

If you have any questions or comments, please don't hesitate to contact us directly. We listen to and read every message sent to us, and we will endeavor to reply promptly to each one. You may call us at 86- 010-82865135. Our mailing address is 1207 Block B of U-Center, No.28 Chengfu Road, Haidian District, Beijing, 100083, P.R.China.
